Still reading?
I've finished comparing them.
I got four multiple-choice questions wrong,
three fill-in-the-blank questions,
and one short answer question.
Hey, don't you need to go to tutoring?
Ah, I'm off.
Zixi, during the exam the other day,
you bought me time.
I
was very touched.
Boss.
Is what you're writing really useful?
Hao.
When dealing with girls,
you must choose every word carefully.
Show-off.
Did you deliver the test answers?
Delivered.
Did she accept them?
I slid them under her door.
She couldn't refuse.
She doesn't know I sent them.
Does she need to know you sent them?
Good thing.
I left a mark.
You made that mark?
Erased it.
I don't think I erased it.
I didn't give you these answers.
I can tell.
The score for these answers is exactly 60, just enough to pass.
Really?
No wonder when I checked them last night,
I felt something was fishy.
Are you done?
I'm sick of doing this.
Tutoring requires a study plan tailored to your level.
Otherwise, it's twice the effort for half the result.
Glad you know.
I'm done.
So many mistakes.
Did you just start learning yesterday?
Not entirely.
I still have some ancient memory points.
What?
Everyone, back to your seats.
Quiet down and get ready for class.
Let's take roll first.
Why isn't Zixi in class?
Guo Long.
Here.
Yang Qian.
Mo Xiaoming.
Here.
Qiu Kexin.
Yin Zixi.
Here.
Yang Chunfeng.
Liang Chen.
Here.
Luo Zicong.
The beginning of this passage is to arouse readers' interest,
and convey facts in concise and clear language
at the same time.
Okay.
Next, five minutes to review the basic characteristics of news.
Senior,
shouldn't the next five minutes be a break?
Reviewing is resting.
What?
Twenty-five minutes of focused study,
and five minutes of review.
After two rounds,
there will be a 15-minute assessment.
This constitutes one study cycle.
Complete 20 cycles today to meet the target.
Hurry up and review.
The basic characteristics of news are truth, freshness, and openness.
Truth is the lifeblood of news,
requiring news to reflect real and objective facts.
Freshness is why news exists.
Yang Qian.
Why hasn't Zixi been coming to class lately?
She's studying for a makeup exam.
What's wrong?
Does she still need to study?
Doesn't she already have the exam answers?
Oh.
So it was you.
What? You don't want her to know?
Not really.
Where is she now?
I wouldn't know about that.
Tell her directly.
Tell her indirectly.
Don't tell her.
You've been counting these three drafts all night.
It's all because of you.
Yes.
Then what can I do?
I am willing to make up for my mistakes.
What can you do?
Ah.
Why are there still security guards patrolling?
Your yelling brought them here.
It's because you didn't wake me up.
I overslept.
Who is it?
Who's there?
I heard your voice.
Come out now.
Follow me.
What was that? Who is it?
Let's go.
Didn't the security guard leave?
Old Chen, I've checked the broadcasting room.
No one is there.
What's wrong?
Campus secret.
This is English written backwards.
Oh.
The senior from your broadcasting station
is quite romantic.
Writing it in such a hidden place,
must have been hard for him.
Yeah.
The security guard should be gone.
It's so late.
I wonder if we can still get into the dorm.
We've fallen behind a lot.
Won't lighting this lamp get us discovered?
I tried it last night.
The brightness is limited.
It can't be seen from outside.
Last night?
Did you think I didn't need to prepare review materials?
Did he start preparing last night?
Why are you spacing out?
We haven't started on the key points here.
So much?
You slept all afternoon.
We should make up for it.
The authenticity of news is
that every specific fact
in the news report.
Must conform to objective reality.
Brother.
Can I refuse?
A gentleman's word
is hard to take back.
Wake up.
Don't study for days
and end up missing the exam.
A small accident.
What small accident?
They even brought a cheer squad for a makeup exam.
Enemies really do cross paths.
Go, Yin Zixi!
Zixi.
Actually, those exam answers
were sent by me.
I did this
actually because...
Boss.
For something this embarrassing,
it'll cost extra.
Isn't it all because of you?
You sent the answers but didn't even leave your name.
If we don't do something now,
wouldn't it be a waste?
Yes.
Hello, everyone.
It's been a while since the last broadcast.
I've recently hit a low point in my life.
I can't see any hope here.
It makes me feel powerless and exhausted.
An unexpected encounter
has made me waver.
It feels like returning to the days when I fought hard.
I started to reflect.
Am I really powerless?
Did I give up too quickly?
Is there really nothing I can do?
Even if I am powerless,
I will give it my all.
I also want to say a few words to the students taking the exam today.
Youth is about running hard,
and then falling gracefully.
But being young gives us the courage to stand back up.
Enjoy falling and getting back up again.
Finally, I wish the students taking the exam today
good luck.
Associate Casting Director Xi Chongjing
Props Assistant Li Kunxiao
Unit Vehicle Yi Mingle
Yitong